NATÁLIA DELGADO ALVES

Product Designer

EXPERIENCE

Lead Product Designer | Wondrfly

JAN 2024, NEW YORK CITY, NY

- Lead the design direction, aligning product goals with user needs and keeping the focus on users
- Drive project success by prioritizing features, establishing design patterns, and resolving design conflicts
- Conduct thorough design reviews to ensure high-quality, user-friendly, and accessible solutions
- Communicate design decisions effectively to product managers, engineers, and executives, securing alignment and collaboration
- Encourage continuous learning and skill growth through mentorship, sharing best practices, and exploring new ideas

Product Designer | Wondrfly

JAN 2023, NEW YORK CITY, NY

- Lead the research and design of new features for the web platform using Figma
- Create responsive sketches, design flows, and high-fidelity prototypes to improve the user experience
- Conduct user interviews to gather feedback for iterative design improvements
- Develop and maintain a comprehensive design system for consistent user experiences
- Contribute to product decisions focusing on the user

UX/UI Designer | Freelancer

JUL 2022 - JAN 2023, CALGARY, AB

- Worked closely with stakeholders to research and design solutions to meet their
- business objectives
- Utilized design thinking methodology to empathize, define, ideate, prototype and test designs for optimal usability
- Conducted user interviews and collected feedback to refine and improve design solutions

Head Coach | Huskies Volleyball Club & Vogo Beach Volleyball

JUN 2020 - 2022, SASKATOON, SK

- Develop and execute volleyball training programs to teach competitive techniques and tactics
- Analyzed athlete performance and identified areas for improvement, providing individual and team feedback
- Support athletes' emotional well-being and identify individual needs for customized training plans

EDUCATION

BrainStation | Diploma, User Experience Design

AUG 2022 - NOV 2022, TORONTO, ON

University Centre of Maringa | Bachelor's in Education

SEP 2012 - 2016, MARINGA, BRAZIL

MY PROJECTS

Product Designer - Wondrfly Platform Web & Mobile | JAN 2023 - Current

nataliacdelgado@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/ natalia-delgado-alves

SKILLS

Figma, HTML, CSS, Google Apps, Teams, Canva, Problem-solving, Teamwork

PROFILE

I'm a UX Designer passionate about making tech easy to use and accessible to everyone. My focus is on creating excellent user experiences that people will love. With experience in user-centred design, I've helped many clients create functional and beautiful interfaces.

CERTIFICATION

Udemy | Certificate, Web Development Bootcamp NOV 2024, CALGARY, AB

University of Alberta | Certificate, Software Product Management JAN 2022, CALGARY, AB

Google | Certificate, UX
Design Professional
JUN 2022, CALGARY, AB

Volleyball Canada |
Certificate, Advanced
Development Coach
JUN 2019, SASKATOON, SK